<?xml version="1.0"?>
<story xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
       xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="story.xsd" title="Le sorcier et la montagne de feu (adapted)">
    <init>Story n°=0</init>
    <step id="BEGIN" type="multiChoice">
        <title>East or West</title>
        <description>Your quest is now starting. After two days of walk you finally reach the mountain of fire.
            What an ominous sigh, the moutain itself seems menacing. Its side seems to have been
            created by the devil himself, lots of crags would scare away even the most seasoned adventurers.
            Atop the mountain you can faintly see a sinister red spreading everywhere -most likely th flaura-
            Crossing the clearing you head straight for the cave acting as an entrance to the moutain.
            It's dark and damp. Only 200 meter inside you are already faced with the path spreading itself in two.
            Where will you go ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s71">Go West.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s278">Go East.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s71" type="multiChoice">
        <title>First encounter... Or is it ?</title>
        <description>After turning west, you walk another 100 meter before coming to a stop before
            what seems to be an improvised guardpost. Discretly you take a quick peek inside and
            see an odd creature not unlike an imp loudly snoring. What should you do ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s301">It's loudly snoring, I can walk past it if I'm careful.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s248">Better not take any chances, I'll make a detour around it.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s278" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A closed door</title>
        <description>The path come to a stop before a locked door. You put you ears close so to
            be able to hear inside. You hear nothing but silence.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s156">Down the door.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s92">Turn back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s301" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Not found out</title>
        <description>You silently walk past the imp. It doesn't wake up and keep snoring. As you keep going,
            a door appear on your left. After listening with your ears close, you can hear a creature
            snoring.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s82">Open the door.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s208">Keep going.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s248" type="memory">
        <theme>default</theme>
        <title>First encounter</title>
        <description>While walking around the guardpost, you step on the least lit area, not knowing where you're
            putting your foot down, you stumble onto the rocks and wake the creature up.
        </description>
        <difficulty>4</difficulty>
        <nextStep value="s301"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s156" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Sturdy door</title>
        <description>Throw a coin. Which side did you got ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s343">Tail.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s92">Face.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s92" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Couldn't break the door</title>
        <description>You didn't manage to break the door. You walk back to the crossroad and head west this time.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s71">Yea..</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s102" type="multiChoice">
        <title>When things go wrong...</title>
        <description>The door open, and you come inside what looks to be a small torture room. Lots of different tools
            that look barbaric are on the wall. At the center of the room, two small creature are torturing a dwarf
            suspended to the ceilling by his wrist. The two monster are cutting him with their swords.
            The dwarf howl a cry and nothing more is heard after his eyes close. The torturer visibly dissatisfied
            by the end of their little experiment, sights and turn themselves toward you with anger as if
            you were the one responsible for the dwarf fainting.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s303">Close the door as humanly possible and keep walking.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s19">Draw your sword and fight the two monsters.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s68">You rush to the dwarf and pierce him while yelling some obscenity.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s208" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Another door</title>
        <description>A little further you find another door on the west wall. You place your ears close but you
            can't hear anything.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s397">Try to open the door.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s363">Keep Walking.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s343" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Door destroyed</title>
        <description>You break through the door and fall face first. You know something is wrong when instead of hitting
            the ground, you keep falling. You finally hit the ground two meter below. Stunned, it takes you several
            seconds before you come to. Standing inside an empty pit with some bruises, you climb back from where you
            came from.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s92">After passing the door you keep walking the same way as before.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s303" type="multiChoice">
        <title>...Turn back as if nothing happened</title>
        <description>You reach the end of the path and stand before an iron portcullis. You won't be able to force it.
            Two lever are sticking out from the wall on your right.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s243">Pull the left lever</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s128">Pull the right lever</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s19" type="memory">
        <theme>default</theme>
        <title>...Fight</title>
        <description>You fight against both creature.
        </description>
        <difficulty>6</difficulty>
        <nextStep value="s317"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s82" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Small room</title>
        <description>The door open and you step inside a small room which smell awfully bad. At the center, a small table
            with a candle, and belo it, a small wooden box. On the right side, far end corner of the room, an ugly
            green creature sleep.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s208">Go back outside and keep walking.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s147">Crawl inside and try to take the box</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s68" type="multiChoice">
        <title>...just pretend they are right</title>
        <description>Both monster exchange a stunned look and turn toward you. They talk, and sign for you to wait
            while they leave to fetch another dwarf. They leave the room. The dwarf on the room is dead as expected.
            You quickly leave the room and keep heading the same way.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s303">Head the same way.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s397" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Empty small room</title>
        <description>The door open. The room on the other side, has a rotten smell to it, and the walls are covered in
            moist. At the center of it, a small table with a candle on it and a wooden box below. On the far end,
            there is a bed made of hay, but no one occupying it.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s240">Head to the center and open the box.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s363">Leave and keep walking.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s363" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Bad singer make for great amusement</title>
        <description>A little further, on the west hand wall, you fin another door just like the previous one
            You try to come close hear anything, but before you can do so, you can hear from the inside
            two voices singing loud and worst as you ever heard. How can one manage to sing so bad ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s370">Step inside to find out.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s42">Keep walking and try to forget what yo just heard</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s243" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Ouch</title>
        <description>What seemed to be a lever is in fact a dagger. You cut yourself on the edge of it, and before long,
            realize there is poison coated on it. You fall to the ground and start agonizing;
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s243badEnd"></choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s243badEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s128" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Open the gate !</title>
        <description>A loud vibration is heard and the portcullis start to rise slowly. You walk past it and can now
            head West or East.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s210">Head West.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s58">Head East.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s317" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Victorious</title>
        <description>You defeat both creature. You then proceed to cut the rope from which the dwarf is suspended.
            As dead as he can be. You leave him there and head back the same way you came.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s303"></choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s147" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Gold coin</title>
        <description>You managed to steal the wooden box. You leave the room and once outside in the corridor,
            you open the box. Inside, you find a gold coin and a mouse that seems to be the pet of the creature you
            just stole the box from. You keep the coin and release the mouse.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s208">You keep walking</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s240" type="memory">
        <theme>fruit</theme>
        <title>...Fight</title>
        <description>The box is light, but somehing doing noise on the inside. You open it and a small snake spring out
            from it. He bite you on the wrist. No choice but to fight it.
        </description>
        <difficulty>3</difficulty>
        <nextStep value="s145"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s370" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Having fun ?</title>
        <description>The door open on a small room. Inside, two small creature wearing leather armor. They rise from
            their seat, but their unsteady footing makes it clear they are drunk.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s116">Take out your sword and jump at them.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s42">Close the door and keep walking.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s42" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Another path to chose</title>
        <description>You reach the end of the road. You can either head West or East. What will it be ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s257">Head West</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s113">Head East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s210" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Open the gate !</title>
        <description>Following the path, you reach yet another bifurcation. This time it's either straight ahead (West),
            or North.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s225">Head West.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s357">Head North.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s58" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Open the gate !</title>
        <description>You carefully crawl along the way. Soon, the path makes a sudden turn toward the North. There is on
            the corner, a sturdy white bench with a sign saying : "Rest here exhausted traveller".
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s15">Can't hurt anyway, let's rest.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s367">Nah, I'm fine, let's keep going.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s145" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A key</title>
        <description>While fighting the snake, you dropped the wooden box on the floor. A bronze key came out of it.
            It's a perfectly normal bronze key, but it has the number '99' written on it.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s363">Take the key and leave.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s116" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fight...</title>
        <description>After rising from their seats, the two creature blankly stare at you. Not knowing why they are not
            attacking, you wait. Before long, the monsters slowly fall to the ground. Not knowing what has happened,
            you carrefully stay where you are. They then start snoring. Being visibly asleep, you carefully examinate
            your surrounding.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s378">Examinate the room.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s257" type="multiChoice">
        <title>More-Door</title>
        <description>The path end with a wooden door. You listen closely, and hear shouts of anger coming from inside.
            Will you head inside to check it out ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s168">Go inside.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s293">Head back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s113" type="multiChoice">
        <title>And again, Another path to chose</title>
        <description>You come to a stop before your path spreading in two.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s285">Head North.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s78">Head East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s225" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Bifurcation</title>
        <description>The path continue West and then make a right turn and head North. A little bit further,
            you arrive at a bifurcation where a small corridor lead to the West.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s77">Head West in the small corridor.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s63">Keep going North.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s357" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Cavern</title>
        <description>The path lead to the North. Soon enought, It spreads out from both side to form an immense cavern
            made of rocks. There doesn't seems to be any exit beside the path you just came from. Should you head back ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s269">Head back to the previous crossroad.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s57">Enter the cavern</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s15" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A little rest is always a good thing</title>
        <description>You rest for a moment and can already feel better. Once you're done eating and drinking, you resume
            your aventure.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s367">Time to leave</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s367" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Bifurcation</title>
        <description>Two path appear before you. Which one will you chose ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s235">Head West</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s8">Head East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s378" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Farrigo Di Maggio</title>
        <description>While examining the room, you find a small box. While examining it more closely it doesn't appear to be
            locked, yet, you can't seem to open it. A small copper plate spell 'Farrigio Di Maggio'. Has you finish
            reading the plate, a small noise can be heard from it. Should you listen to it ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s378a">Listen to it.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s42">Drop the box and leave.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s378a" type="riddle">
        <title>Magic Box</title>
        <description>If you have me, you want to share me. If you share me, you haven’t got me. What am i?</description>
        <hint>Everyone has some</hint>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s296">Secret</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s296">A secret</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s168" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Imp master</title>
        <description>The door open on a big room. A chair made of quality wood, and a massive table makes it clear that
            someone or something important is occupying this room. At the center of the room, you see a chest.
            On the far end side, An imp two times bigger than the average is holding a whip and lashing a smaller one.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s372">Fight both of them.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s65">Fight the chief and hope the small one will help you.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s293">Leave the room and head back to the junction</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s293" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Junction</title>
        <description>You're back at the junction and head East this time.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s113">Go East.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s285" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Pleading</title>
        <description>On the right side of the path (East), there is a door. You can hear on the other side of it
            a man calling for help. Will you help him ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s36">Open the door to help him.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s300">Keep going</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s78" type="multiChoice">
        <title>That's a big door</title>
        <description>The path ends before a massive door made of wood and hinge made of metal. You can hear someone
            mumbling inintelligble words, and pots bonking each other. There is no doubt that there are several people
            in there. This is most probably the eating room for all the creatur
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s159">Head inside.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s237">Head back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s77" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Getting hungry ?</title>
        <description>After walking several meter in the passageway, you stop before a crossing. As always, you can either
            head West or head East.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s18">Head West.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s311">Head East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s63" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Is it getting narrow, or is it just me ?</title>
        <description>You walk along the path and the further you are walking, the more it's getting narrow. After
            some times, the ceilling is also getting lower until you have to crouch to be able to keep going.
            At the same time you are thinking that, a laught echo all around you.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s281">Keep going.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s10">Head Back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s269" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Back</title>
        <description>You are back to previous junction.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s225">Head west.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s57" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Inside the cavern</title>
        <description>At the same moment you walk inside the cavern, you hear loud footstep behind you. You crouch in
            a dark corner near the entrance. The footsteps are getting louder and louder. and an Ogre measuring no less
            than two meter come in view, he's holding a mass on his right hand. It has not yet found you out
            but he is getting close. He seems to have some trouble walking in the path leading to the cavern.
            He should have some trouble swinging his mass there. What will you do ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s57a">Fight him before he gets inside.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s269">Throw a rock on the far side of the cavern to distract him while you slip by.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s57a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fighting</title>
        <description>YOu confront the ogre while he is at a disadventage. He has trouble moving forward, and swinging his
            mass in this closed space is impossible. You carefully face him. The orgre reach for his mass and pull it
            the best he can in this narrow corridor. In the meantime, you strike it's right tight. A loud groan makes
            it clear that it must have hurt. Not knowing how to defend himself the Ogre flay his legs toward you.
            'Wait what ??!!' taken completly by surprise you are hit by a massive leg coming in your direction.
            Stunned, the ogre proceed to rush toward you and seize you in on of it's hand. Before you know it. You have
            been squashed against the wall.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s57badEnd">....</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s57badEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s235" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Bifurcation</title>
        <description>Two path appear before you. Which one will you chose ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s176">Head West</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s218">Head North</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s8" type="memory">
        <theme>prof</theme>
        <title>Barbarian</title>
        <description>The path ends with a sturdy door. You try to listen, but no sound are made on the other side.
            You turn the handle and step inside. As you are looking around, a war cry  resound behind you. You
            instantly turn and face the barbarian rushing toward you.
        </description>
        <difficulty>5</difficulty>
        <nextStep value="s273"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s296" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Success</title>
        <description>You managed to find the solution. The box open, and inside, you find a small codex titled
            'How does the dragon make and blows fire'. The book is without a doubt very precious. The author,
            'Farrigo Di Maggio' expose one of the most important work of his life. It explains accurately how dragon
            are able to breathe fire and teach you a spell to neutralize this ability. You memorize the formula,
            and before you know it, the codex pages fade to white...
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s42">Head back outside</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s372" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fight</title>
        <description>You engage the fight engage the two of them. On which one should you focus your attention first ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s372a">The Imp Master</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s372badEnd">The small Imp</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s372a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fight</title>
        <description>You fight the Imp master first. It still only has a whip in his hand and you kill him before he has
            time to reach for the sword on his side. By the time you are done with him, the small one wounded only had
            time to square himself off. Already weakened, he is not a threat to you. You make short work of him
            and ends him easily.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s21">Proceed</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s65" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fight</title>
        <description>You focus your attention on the Imp master while hoping that the small one will help you by
            taking his revenge against his persecutor. As you rush for the Master, unexpectedly, the small one
            jump in the melee and side with his master.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s372">Fight both of them.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s36" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Pleading</title>
        <description>You open the door and find an old man sprawnled on the ground. He is not on a good shape, and he is
            wounded. He see you at the entrance and ask for help. He says he knows valuable information that could help
            you.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s36a">Reach to help him.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s300">He's done for, leave him there and keep going.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s36a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Helping</title>
        <description>You reach to help the old man but as you crouch to help him stand up, he pulls a knife from his
            sleeves and attacks you while yelling like a mad man. He cuts you on your left flank.
            You rise and distance yourself from him. What will you do ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s300">Leave him there</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s36b">Crouch down again and try to help him again</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s263">Yell the loudest you can and tell him to silence himself</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s36b" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Helping</title>
        <description>You reach down again to help the old man, this times he aim for the neck. You bleed out.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s36abadEnd">...</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s36abadEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s300" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A door</title>
        <description>A little bit further, on the West side of the path, you find a door. On the other side of it, you can
            hear scream coming from someone probably being tortured. Should you open the door ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s102">Open the door.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s303">Keep going</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s159" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Eating room</title>
        <description>You head inside the eating room. You push the door and it resound loudly. Once the door open,
            you gaze inside the room and everyone's eyes are headed your way. You only have time to pull out your sword
            before dozens of Imp are fighting you. You bravely defeat ten of them but still fall to the unending influx
            of monsters.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s159badEnd">Head inside.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s159badEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s237" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Walking</title>
        <description>You walk back  along the path and head to the previous bifurcation. This time, you head North.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s285">North It is.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s18" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crumbling ground</title>
        <description>You walk toward the West along the path. After 50 meters or so, you feel the ground slighly rumbling
            in front of you. Some of the path is clearly crumbling and the rest is still in place by some kind
            of luck.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s261">Head Back to the previous crossroad</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s18a">I've been losing wait recently. I should be able to cross...</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s18a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Not so ligh after all</title>
        <description>You confidently walk forward. The The first step you take, the ground crumble below your feet,
            and you end up falling in a stake hole.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s18abadEnd">....</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s18abadEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s311" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Water is echoing</title>
        <description>You walk along the path. The more you progress forward, the more the sound of a river is making itself
            heard. Soon enought, you stand before a large river.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s244">Head West.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s244" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A river</title>
        <description>You stand before the river. The current is strong enought to pull you with him
            and you can't see what's downriver.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s143">Rest here while thinking of a solution.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s399">Jump in the river and head downstream.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s281" type="multiChoice">
        <title>It's too narrow</title>
        <description>The path becomes so narrow that you can't progresss any further. You turn tail and head back to the
            crossroads.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s10">Head Back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s10" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Junction</title>
        <description>You are back to the crossroad and head North.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s77">North, got it.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s176" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Cavern</title>
        <description>At some point, you reach a cavern entrance. The cavern is 30 meter wide, and there is no apparent
            exit on the other side.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s270">Head inside</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s375">Go back to the junction</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s270" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Exploring the Cavern</title>
        <description>You explore the cavern and find dozens of stalactite and stalagmite of beautiful color surrounding
            the place. At the end of the cavern, you find a pair of boot recently made.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s61">Keep exploring.</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s375">Head back.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s61" type="multiChoice">
        <title>A noble... spider ?</title>
        <description>While exploring the cavern, you suddently hear behind you a set of hasty footsteps. Before you have
            time to pull out your sword, the giant spider salutes you with one of it's forelegs. Unepexctedly, it can
            talk. and pronounce the following words in a dignified tone not unlike a noble :
            "It's been so long since I had someone visiting. Dear sir, would you kindly wagger over a riddle with me ?
            Should you win, I will tell you somethings that might come in handy for your adventure" What will
            you answer ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s61a">"Sure let's play"</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s61c">Say nothing and flee as fast as you can</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s61a" type="riddle">
        <title>Let's play !</title>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is the riddle :</p>
            <p>“To all things and men I appertain,</p>
            <p>and yet by some am shunned and distained.</p>
            <p>Fondle me and ogle me til you’re insane,</p>
            <p>but no blow can harm me, cause me pain.</p>
            <p>Children delight in me, elders take fright.
            <p>Fair maids rejoice and spin.</p>
            <p>Cry and I weep, yawn and I sleep.</p>
            <p>Smile, and I too shall grin.</p>
            <p>What am I?”</p>
        ]]>
        </description>
        <hint>Everyone has one but you can't always see it</hint>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s61a1">Reflection</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s61a1">The reflection</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s61a1" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Success</title>
        <description>Delighted you found the answer the spider talks "It is indeed a reflection ! My quite a smart
            adventurer you are. A wagger's a wagger. Here is what I promised you. If you wish to reach the top of the
            mountain, you need but to listend for the flow of water. Follow the sound and once you reach the river,
            ring the bell. Make sure you pay the men so you can cross safely". The spider then salute's you once again
            and go back to the darkness. Did it seemed disapointed that you won ? You head back and follow the spider advice to listen dor the sound of water.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s218">Head back and follow the advice</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s61c" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Fleeing</title>
        <description>Before you know it, the spider is standing before you and you are bleeding out. Loosing consciousness, you hear the last
            word of the spider. "That's too bad. Let's hope the next one will be better"
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s61cbadEnd">...</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s61cbadEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s218" type="multiChoice">
        <title>The river</title>
        <description>You reach the shore and before you, flow a river. The current is strong, and the dwonstream is engulfed
            in darkness. There seem to be four way of crossing the river. On your left a rusty bell, in front, a small
            boat is attached, on the right, an old bridge not spared by the time, and you can still try to swim accross.
            Which one will you choose ?
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s3">Ring the bell</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s386">Use the boat</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s209">Try to cross the bridge</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s316">Swim</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s273" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Victory</title>
        <description>You defeated the barbarian. You keep walking and come before an open door. Passing through, before
            long you hear the song of water flowing.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s218">Let's keep going</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s372badEnd" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Bad choice</title>
        <description>You fight the small Imp first. You dispatch him easily, but by the time you are done, the Imp master
            has already dropped the whip and pulled out a sword. You try to fight the master, but stumble on the body
            of the imp recently defeated. The Imp master doesn't let this opportunity go to waste.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s372badEnda">...</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s372badEnda" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s21" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Victory</title>
        <description>You defeated both the monster. You now turn your attention to the chest. It's locked, but you could
            try to force it open with your sword.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s339">Force the chest open</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s293">Leave it there and head back</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s339" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Chest open</title>
        <description>You managed to open the chest. Inside you find 25 gold coins, a bottle of unknown liquid, and a glove
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s293">Take the items and leave</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s263" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Yelling</title>
        <description>You yell the loudest you can to silence him. Stunned, he look at you and calms himself. After some
            time has passed and he is calm enought, you decide to talk with him. You ask him if he would like to
            follow you, but he politely decline. You learn that he has been emprisoned here after going on a
            quest just like you. Before you both part way, he tells you to be respectfull to the boatmen and
            that you should pull the right lever when you reach the portcullis. You both part way. You leave the room
            and head the same direction.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s300">Keep going</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s261" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Turning back</title>
        <description>You turn back and head to the previous junction, heading East this time.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s345">East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s345" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crumbled path</title>
        <description>As you wal you reach what seems to be a junction. But the path forward is crumbled. You have no
            choice but to head East.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s311">East</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s143" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Resting</title>
        <description>You lay down to rest for a moment. While thinking of something, the ground below you start
            shaking. You jump to the side to avoid the worm coming out of the ground and prepare to fight him.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s143a">Fight</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s143a" type="memory">
        <theme>prof</theme>
        <title>Worm fight</title>
        <description>You put your guard up and face the worm.
        </description>
        <difficulty>6</difficulty>
        <nextStep value="s143b"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s143b" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Tough fight</title>
        <description>The fight prooved to be harder than you imagined. You manage to inflict serious wound on the worm
            but had no choice than to jump on the water.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s399">Fight</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s399" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Swiming</title>
        <description>The current is strong and it's pulling you downstream. You are taken through an opening on the cavern
            walls, and arrive in another cavern. The current then push you on the South shore.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s218">Stand up</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s3" type="multiChoice">
        <title>The bell is ringing</title>
        <description>The bell is faintly ringing and a men appear on the opposite shore. He climbs in a small boat just
            like the one on your side and cross slowly but steadily the river. After some time, he reach your your side
            and tie his boat to your side of the shore. He talks to you and require 3 Gold coin to make you cross
            to the other side.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s272">Pay him his due</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s127">Threaten him to let you pass for free</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s272" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crossing the river</title>
        <description>You pay the old man his price. You get on the old man boat and cross the river with him. After some
            time, you reach the other side of the river and you part way with him.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s272a">Continue</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s272a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crossing the river</title>
        <description>Congratulation, You managed to cross the river and are getting closer to the top of the mountain.
            That's it for this story. Thank you for playing.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s272agoodEnd">Continue</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s272agoodEnd" type="end">
        <description>You won</description>
        <win value="true"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s127" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Old mand fight</title>
        <description>The old mand doesn't bulge an inch while you threaten him. After some time, his skin starts to turn
            Dark and hair starts to grow from all over his body. He also seems to now be taller than you and sturdily
            built. Before you can do anything, the old man simply pushes you on the water.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s316">Try to swim</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s386" type="multiChoice">
        <title>The boat</title>
        <description>You step on the boat and start rowing to reach the other side. Halfway through, the boat start to
            move on it's own and capsize. You try to swim to the other side, but can't make it.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s316">Swim</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s209" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crossing the bridge</title>
        <description>You go to the bridge and try to avoid thinking of how old it is. By the time you reach halfway, the
            bridge rumble and you heard some plank falling on the water behind you.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s209a">Start running to the other side</choice>
            <choice nextStep="s209b">Keep walking</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s209a" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crossing the bridge</title>
        <description>You run the fatest you can to reach to the other side of the bridge. Unfortunatly, it crumbles under
            your feet and you ends up in the water.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s316">Swim</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s209b" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Crossing the bridge</title>
        <description>You calmy walk to the ohter side while not paying attention to the bridge that is entirely crumbling
            behind you. By some kind of miracle, you managed to reach the other side.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s272a">Continue</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s316" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Swimming against the current</title>
        <description>You try your hardest to swim to the other side of the shore, but the current is just too strong.
            The water slowly drags you to the dark opening where you can hear a waterfall. Soon, you are completly
            exhausted, and end up falling of the waterfall.
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s316badEnd">...</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
    <step id="s316badEnd" type="end">
        <description>You died</description>
        <win value="false"/>
    </step>
    <step id="s375" type="multiChoice">
        <title>Junction</title>
        <description>You head back to the junction and head North
        </description>
        <possibility>
            <choice nextStep="s218">Continue.</choice>
        </possibility>
    </step>
</story>
